PRAYER TIME
Stretch your hand.
Are you in an attitude of prayer?
Like I have said,
faith releases healing power.
Faith releases blessing.
Faith is like a vacuum that draws anointing from God.
You're building faith.
You are like a ball - it is pumped but it is not well pumped.
But the more you are saying, take more of me, give me more of you, you are pumping the ball.
Take more of me, give me more of you. You see the ball becoming big.
You are the ball.
So if you stop, you stop pumping.
And if you continue, the ball will continue to grow big.
You are the ball.
The air that enters is that faith.
The word you are saying - take more of me, give me more of you - it's so strong.
It's spirit prayer.
When you get that ball to stand and at the level you can play it, you begin to eat with Jesus.
see visions and dream dreams.
Your heart will begin to talk to you.
You don't need to sleep to see vision; it's the heart that talks to us.
You'll be moving. Your heart would say, Don't go there, go back.
Who is talking to you?
It's your heart, pumped by faith - get it working.
See with your heart and not with your eye.
Stretch your hand.
Every barrier between your heart and the Spirit of God, be broken, in Jesus' name!
[Amen]
We want to fight this barrier.
Whatever barrier between your heart and the Spirit of God, be removed, in the name of Jesus!
[Amen]
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
What could be the barrier? - It could be offence you are holding against your neighbour.
You say, over your dead body, you will not forgive!
Are you holding an offence, grudges, hatred, bitterness or pain of the past?
Be removed, in the name of Jesus!
I want you to stretch your hand and begin to remove whatever satan might have used to connect you.
He uses offence to connect us. He uses grudges to connect us to himself.
He uses pain of the past to connect us to himself. He uses bitterness to connect us to himself.
Whatever satan might have used to connect you to himself, begin to disconnect yourself!
Disconnect yourself!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I want to believe you are with a free spirit.
A free spirit is a spirit that joins with the Spirit of God.
Right now.
Whatever strange spirit around, within or outside,
we want to put them where they belong, we want to tell them where they should go.
Right now.
Every familiar spirit!
[Out!]
You familiar spirit!
Every familiar spirit!
[Out!]
Whatever spirit - within or outside that torments your business, life, that stands in your way -
be cursed, in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Every knee, in the name of Jesus!
Every enemy shall surrender, in the name of Jesus!
Every enemy shall surrender.
I say to your enemy - surrender!
Surrender!
Enemy of progress,
enemy of your health,
enemy of your finances,
enemy of your business,
enemy of your career,
enemy of your future,
enemy of your destiny,
enemy of your family,
enemy of your marriage,
enemy of your country!
Open your lips!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
All enemies shall surrender when hearing the name of Jesus.
Why should yours not surrender?
In the name of Jesus!
Holy Ghost fire!
All enemies shall surrender, including yours. Put them where they belong!
Command them!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I destroyed her!
Who are you in this body?
I'm a giant man. I want to kill her.
What have you done to her?
I caused her barrenness; I want to destroy her.
We are soldiers
Soldiers of the Lord
In the name of Jesus we shall conquer
We are soldiers
Soldiers of the Lord
In the name of Jesus we shall conquer
We are soldiers
Soldiers of the Lord
In the name of Jesus we shall conquer
We are soldiers
Soldiers of the Lord
In the name of Jesus we shall conquer
We are soldiers
Soldiers of the Lord
In the name of Jesus we shall conquer
In the name of Jesus we have conquered
Give thanks to God and believe it is done!
It is done!
Give thanks to Him!
I pray that the Lord exposes your weakness and delivers you!
[Amen]
Every weakness - be exposed and be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
I say, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
[Amen]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I can see you being delivered!
[Amen]
You have been delivered, in the name of Jesus!
You have been set free, in the name of Jesus!
Do you know what it means when an anointed man of God says you have been set free?
Now in this case, the choice is yours.
You can choose to say, "I have been set free". You can choose to say, "No, I am not yet set free".
You have been set free, in the name of Jesus!
[Amen]
I can see you walking in liberty!
I can see you walking in freedom!
[Amen]
I can see you walking in breakthrough!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Let the people of God say 'Amen'!
[Amen]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The question is, do you know yourself?
Do you know you have been delivered?
Tell your neighbour, do you know yourself? Do you know you have been delivered?
Do you believe that?
Let me see your excitement!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
Because I'm happy that you have been set free!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Amen!
Thank you, I'm happy. I'm happy for your life.
Wave your flag.
Begin to pray for your nation.
Ask God to redeem your nation, your country.
Redeem my nation. Redeem my country.
Oh Lord, redeem my leader.
Prayer For The Nations With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Every attack of the enemy,
corruption,
misappropriation,
idolatry,
misrule,
misjudge.
Ask God to redeem your nation.
Say, Lord, redeem my nation.
Redeem my leaders.
Redeem my nation.
Every effort of the enemy, every weapon of the enemy used to attack my nation -
corruption, misappropriation, misrule, misjudge, idolatry.
Right now, begin to pray for your nation. Ask God to redeem your nation.
God intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
[Amen]
I can't hear you!
Give thanks to God!
Right now, begin to confess whom you are.
Yes.
Those of you that have come for the first time
and you are knowing Jesus for the first time, say after me:
Lord Jesus, I am a sinner, come into my heart,
wash me with Your precious blood, save my soul.
Lord Jesus, You are my Saviour.
Thank You for my salvation.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Wave your hand and say, Thank You, Lord.
Hallelujah!